gorillaservers.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy - GorillaServers Inc.

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the https://www.gorillaservers.com and GorillaServers Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to GorillaServers Inc include https://www.gorillaservers.com and GorillaServers. The GorillaServers website is a Dedicated Servers site. By using the GorillaServers website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

 **Collection of your Personal Information:**

GorillaServers may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase GorillaServers's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by GorillaServers. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the GorillaServers website. 

GorillaServers encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from GorillaServers so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. GorillaServers is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the GorillaServers website. 

**Use of your Personal Information** :

GorillaServers collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. 

GorillaServers may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from GorillaServers and its affiliates. GorillaServers may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

GorillaServers does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

GorillaServers may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to GorillaServers, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

GorillaServers may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within GorillaServers, in order to determine what GorillaServers services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within GorillaServers to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

GorillaServers will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on GorillaServers or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of GorillaServers; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of GorillaServers, or the public. 

**Security of your Personal Information :**

GorillaServers secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. 

**Children Under Thirteen:**

GorillaServers does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

**Changes to this Statement :**

GorillaServers will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. GorillaServers encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how GorillaServers is protecting your information. 

**Contact Information :**

GorillaServers welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that GorillaServers has not adhered to this Statement, please contact GorillaServers at: 

GorillaServers Inc 800 S. Hope St, Suite B10 Los Angeles, California 90017 

**Effective as of October 14, 2015**
